《尖叫皇后》前情提要
Previously on Scream Queens...
尖叫皇后 S02E10
字幕由SSK字幕組傾情譯制
字幕僅供學習，勿用於商
轉載請註明出處，版權歸片方所有
SSK字幕組
新浪微博@SSK字幕組
官網：www.sskzmz.com
看來我們需要開一個綠衣惡鬼峰會了
Looks like we're gonna need to call a Green Meanie summit.
SSK字幕組
我們要回顧過去殺人情況並制定未來的計劃
We are here to review the past and future kills.
夏奈爾·奧伯林油炸了我姐姐的臉
Chanel Oberlin fried my sister's face off.
救我
Help me!
我是夏奈爾三號 卡西迪的女朋友
I'm Chanel #3, Cassidy's girlfriend.
她必須去死
She is going to have to die.
我們可以把丹妮斯放進冷櫃裏
We can put Denise in the freezer
直到他們找到治療電擊的方法
until they find a cure for being electrocuted.
你 布洛克·霍爾特醫生 是一個殺手
You, Dr. Brock Holt, are a killer.
我得了苦魯病
I have a disease called Kuru.
是晚期 一個月後我就會死
It is terminal. I'll be dead in a month.
你們想要殺了我 是嗎
You guys are gonna kill me, aren't you?
夏奈爾
Chanel?
我的老天
Holy crap!
對不起
I'm sorry.
-你還好嗎 -還好
- Are you okay? - Yeah.
謝謝你沒有殺我
Thanks for not killing me.
我不想再這樣下去了
I don't want this anymore.
那你媽媽怎麼辦
What about your mom, though?
我會殺了她
I'm gonna have to kill her.
那樣似乎有些極端吧
Doesn't that seem a little extreme?
你和她談談怎麼樣
How about you just talk to her?
噢 好
Oh, yeah.
那可能也行得通
That could work, too.
你不殺我 還反抗你媽媽的行為
You not killing me and standing up to your mom
完全勾起了我的興致
is totally turning me on.
我回家飛快洗個戰鬥澡
How 'bout I go home and take a quick whore's bath
然後我們一個半小時後見怎麼樣
and you meet me in a half an hour?
呃
Mm...
嗯行
mm-Kay.
待會兒見
I'll see you then.
哦我的天
Oh, my gosh.
這些夏奈爾好難殺
These Chanels are impossible to kill.
好像她們的自戀和愚蠢
It's almost like their narcissism
創造出了某種圍繞她們的
and stupidity create some kind
無形的力場
of a force field around them.
我們必須謀劃得更周密
We have to think bigger.
然後我們要盡快實施計劃
And we've got to make that happen, soon.
我不幹了 行嗎
I'm out, okay?
我受夠了
I'm-I'm-I'm done.
現在 所有的你來做吧
This is all you, now.
除了夏奈爾三號
Except for Chanel #3.
如果你動了她
If you touch her,
那我很樂意重新出手
then I'll gladly come out of retirement
來做掉你
to end you.
聽著 小男孩兒
Listen up, pretty boy.
如果你不參與解決她們的計劃
If you're not part of the solution,
那麼在我看來
then as far as I'm concerned,
你就是另一個大問題
you are just another problem.
尖叫皇后
翻譯  菌菌
緊急呼叫霍菲護士
Call E.C.C. Nurse Hoffel, call E.C.C.
我們今晚還是一起吃飯嗎
We still on for dinner tonight?
我有些疑惑
I'm a little bit confused as to
為什麼我們還要一起約會
whether we're still dating.
翻譯  流光
我是說 我以前想要掐死你
I mean, I did try to strangle you
所以我完全能夠理解
and I would totally understand
如果你認為那種行為有那麼點兒
if you thought that was sort of,
呃 越界了
uh, crossing the line.
確實 但不要誤會
It was, don't get me wrong.
翻譯  默默吼
在交往那麼長時間後
But there comes a point in every long-term relationship
你真的可能就想
where you feel like you just want to...
掐死你的伴侶
strangle your partner!
翻譯  jennifer
結果 你確實那麼做了
So, the fact that you actually did,
這意味著我們互相交流著那些感受
means we are communicating those feelings
而不是把它們深藏心底
instead of burying them.
另外 既然你
Plus, I took the fact
幫助我 三號和五號作弊
that you helped me, Number Three and Number Five
翻譯  君故
通過醫學考試 我就當作你真誠地道歉了
cheat on the MCATs as your way of truly apologizing.
你們沒有幫我作弊
You didn't help me cheat!
沒人幫我作弊
Nobody helped me cheat!
我差一點兒就優秀 這都是靠我自己
I almost got a perfect score all by myself.
我們都差一點兒就優秀了呢 五號
We all almost got perfect scores, Number Five.
校對  音帆
但是我沒有作弊
But I didn't cheat!
沒人在意
Nobody cares!
總之
Anyway,
我們還是一起吃晚飯吧
we still on for dinner?
好啊
Sure.
為什麼你對就在你眼前的機會
Why can't you see the opportunity
視而不見
right in front of you?
唯一就在我眼前的
The only thing I see right in front of me
時軸 hhjie
是一個治療得不錯的褥瘡
is a bedsore that's progressing quite nicely,
洛克萊爾先生
Mr. Locklear.
好了 我繼續給你開
All right, I want to keep you on, uh,
壓制  hhjie
磺胺銀軟膏和夫喃西林
silver sulfadiazine and nitrofurazone
在我們進行另一次清創術之前
for a few more days, before we attempt
你再多用幾天這些藥 好吧
another debridement, huh?
蒙施教務長快死了
Dean Munsch is dying.
很快
And soon.
總監  熠熠
她的財產按照遺囑會給
And her fortune is going into a trust
一個委託人 前提是
that's being drafted on the premise
她沒有近親了
that she doesn't have a next of kin.
她的確沒有
Which she doesn't,
但是會有的 只要你說服她
but she will, when you convince her
-嫁給你 -什麼
- to marry you. - What?
想一想吧
Just... think about it.
你倆結婚了
You two get hitched,
她被苦魯病折騰死了
she kicks it from the Kuru
然後砰
and bam!
你就是財產托管人了
You're the fortune's trustee.
如果我成為委託人
If I'm in charge of the trust...
我們把財產從那幫糊塗蛋手中奪過來
We'll rob it from them blind.
我們一起私奔
We'll run away together.
到很遠很遠的 沒人能找到我們的地方
Far, far away, where no one can find us.
我們在海灘邊修理小船
We'll fix up a boat on the beach,
就像《肖申克的救贖》的最後一幕
just like the last scene in Shawshank.
不 我不是很喜歡船
No, I don't really like boats.
聽著 我們可以買下血島
Listen, we can buy Blood Island.
我們一起住在那裏
We'll live there together.
只有兩個殺人兇手 沒人可殺
Just two murderers with no one to murder
除了彼此 但是我們永遠不會下手
except for each other, but we never will,
因為我們深愛並信任彼此
because we love and trust each other.
相信我 布洛克
And believe me, Brock,
沒人像我那麼理解你
no one understands you like I do.
我會永遠在這裏等你
I will always be there for you.
而且我會永遠
And I will always...
讓你干我
let you attack my crack.
甚至是當我吃大餐的時候
Even when I've had a really large meal
我也不確定你在我這兒還有什麼新發現喔
and I'm unsure of what you might encounter up there.
算了
Now you lost me.
我們可以買下
We can buy
血島 然後我們可以吸引來
Blood Island and we can fill it
一船一船的遊客
with boatloads of tourists.
然後我們可以把他們一個接一個殺掉
Then we'll knock 'em off one by one
類似《死亡遊戲》
Most Dangerous Game style.
極限旅遊最近挺火的
Extreme tourism is quite hot right now.
是吧
See?
是的 但是這個計劃太複雜了
Yeah, but this plan is too elaborate.
如果你停下來想一想
If you stop and think about it...
別想了
Don't think about it.
這個計劃
This plan
看上去不太可能
seems impossible
除非我們實施它
until it's possible.
實際上
In fact,
它是必然的
it's inevitable.
好的 好了
Okay. All right.
我會 呃
I'll, uh,
我會考慮的
I'll think about it.
莫比烏斯
Moebius?
我叫達瑞亞 達瑞亞·詹森
It's Daria. Daria Janssen.
管你是誰 你在這裏幹嘛呢
Whatever. What are you doing out here?
好吧
Well,
我喜歡新鮮的番茄
I love fresh tomatoes.
我測過了這片地的pH值
I checked the pH of the swamp,
得出了結論 土壤底部
and concluded that the rich humus
富含腐殖質
that settles at the bottom
會成為極好的
would make a fantastic
-富氮肥料 -這些
-nitrogen-rich fertilizer. -The...
番茄似乎長得不怎麼好
tomatoes appear to be glowing slightly.
別點火
Don't light that!
肥料是易燃物
This stuff is highly flammable.
一點火星
One spark and
就能讓我們被炸死
that much fertilizer would kill us both.
明白嗎
Duh.
明白
怎樣製作肥料炸彈
搜索一下
網頁已鎖定
你是恐怖分子嗎?
是                                  否
我是恐怖分子
我不是恐怖分子
噢我的天哪 粗大事了粗大事了
Oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God.
-怎麼了 -好了 聽著
-What? -Okay, get this.
昨晚 我在霍爾特醫生家裏待了一晚
Last night, I spent the night at Dr. Hot's house
他一睡著 我就抓起他的手機
and as soon as he fell asleep, I snatched his phone
然後翻看了幾個小時
and started going through it for hours and hours.
等下 你不應該那麼做吧
Wait. Are you supposed to do that?
嘿 他是我男朋友
Hello? He's my boyfriend.
他相信我不會做那種事的
He trusts me enough not to do that kind of thing,
所以我做那種事就更容易了
which makes it really easy for me to do that kind of thing.
你完全忽視了男女關係是如何運作的
Your total ignorance about how relationships work
這可能是你所有男朋友
is probably the reason why
都被殺了的原因
all your boyfriends get murdered.
什麼 那和
What? That has nothing
我男朋友們被殺沒有任何關係
to do with my boyfriends being murdered.
好吧 繼續催眠你自己吧
Yeah. Keep telling yourself that.
總之
Anyway,
我看了他的搜索歷史
I went through his browser history
他谷歌了
and he was googling...
便宜的訂婚戒指
cheap engagement rings.
「怎樣才能
"How quickly
很快得到一個便宜的訂婚戒指」
can I get a cheap engagement ring?"
我是說 你們明白這代表著什麼嗎
I mean, do you know what this means?
噢我的老天
Oh, my God.
布洛克要向我求婚了
Brock is gonna propose to me!
噢我的老天
Oh, my God!
閉嘴
Shut up!
霍爾特醫生讓所有人
Dr. Holt is asking everyone
在蒙施教務長的病房集合
to gather in Dean Munsch's room.
夏奈爾 我很高興你來了
Chanel, I'm glad you're here.
我很高興大家都來了
I'm glad everyone's here.
我知道這聽起來很瘋狂 但是
I know this sounds crazy, but...
我就是要這麼做
I'm just gonna do it,
因為人生太短暫
'cause life is too short.
確實
It is!
你能嫁給我嗎
Will you marry me?
凱西
Cathy?
噢
Oh...
-啥 -我只是
- What?! - I just...
我沒想到會發生這事
I wasn't expecting this to happen.
沒人想到會發生這事
Nobody was expecting this to happen!
凱西 就讓你人生的最後一段時光
Cathy, let's enjoy the last few days of your life
更快樂些吧
the way you should.
你和我結為夫妻
You and I, as man and wife.
是上床的那種嗎
Pounding?
是的 親愛的
Yes, darling. Pounding.
我願意
Yes.
我當然願意
Of course.
我願說一千遍我願意
A thousand times, yes.
哦
Oh...
治癒醫療研究院
夏奈爾
Chanel?
哦 夏奈爾
Oh, Chanel,
抱歉 我應該提前告訴你的
I'm sorry. I should have told you I was gonna do that.
你竟然跟我的死敵求婚
Propose to my mortal enemy?
你至少應該
I think telling me about it
提前告訴我
was the least you could have done.
你為什麼要這麼做
What is happening?
蒙施教務長一個月內就要死了
Oh, Dean Munsch is gonna die in a month,
最多一個月
tops. I mean,
你就把我的求婚當成是一種
think of my proposal as sort of...
臨終關愛
end-of-life care.
浪漫的臨終服務
Like a romantic hospice.
像是許願基金會那樣的東西嗎
Like, a Make-A-Wish Foundation kind of thing?
沒錯
Yes, exactly.
就像是許願基金會那樣
Like a Make-A-Wish Foundation thing.
這不公平
It's not fair!
我也要死了
I mean, I'm dying, too.
從某種角度看 我們會死
We all are, in a way.
我想要個帥帥的醫生男朋友
I mean, I want a hot doctor boyfriend.
有個男朋友對你來說到底有什麼意思
What does having a boyfriend even mean to you?
你明顯不是為了上床
You're clearly not into sex.
而你想要的
But what you are into
只是找個人一起拍可愛的情侶照 然後傳到網上
is having someone to post adorable relationship selfies with.
社交網站上的愛情足跡對我很重要
My romantic social media footprint is very important to me.
我知道 所以
I know it is. And that's
我們以後每天見三次面
why we're gonna meet up three times a day,
拍一些可愛的照片
and we're gonna take cute-as-button
你可以貼一些狗狗的貼紙在上面
pictures and-and you can put the dog filter on,
豎著耳朵伸著舌頭那種
with the ears and the big
然後寫些亂七八糟的東西
tongue and write silly little things on it.
假裝我們是真的情侶一樣 上傳到網站上
And you post it just like we're a real couple.
因為我們就是真的情侶
Because we are a real couple.
-好吧 -可以嗎
- Okay. - Okay?
然後 有可能
And then, maybe...
只是有可能
just maybe...
等蒙施教務長死了
when Dean Munsch dies,
我就把戒指從她冰冷的手指上擼下來 送給你
I'll rip that ring off her cold, dead finger and give it to you.
媽媽
Mom.
你看到夏奈爾三號還活著 就可能知道我要說什麼了
As you can tell from Chanel #3 still being alive...
我決定
I have decided
不再殺人了
that I don't want to kill anymore.
所有人都認為格蕾絲的怪物老爸是殺手
Everyone thinks Grace's creepy dad was the killer.
如果從現在開始不再有謀殺出現
If no one else gets murdered from now on,
你就可以逃之夭夭了
you basically got away with it all.
我很愛你 媽媽
I love you so much, Mom.
真的很愛
I do.
但我是個治癒者
But I'm a healer.
所有的這些殺人和復仇
All this killing and revenge stuff,
都是你的想法
it's... it's you.
不是我
It's not me.
直到醫院關閉的那天 這事才能結束
This ends when the hospital is shut down.
別想阻攔我
Don't try and get in my way.
你怎麼能那樣跟你的兒子說話
How can you talk to your son like that?
他不是我的兒子
He's no son of mine.
他是你的了 蕩婦
He's all yours, Jezebel.
你對剛才的事怎麼想
How do you feel about what just happened?
我知道我是正確的
I know I'm right.
你的愛告訴我我是正確的
Your love has shown me that.
但我們有個更大的難題
But we have a bigger problem.
霍菲
Hoffel.
她是另一個綠衣惡鬼
She's the other Green Meanie.
我覺得她在謀劃更大的陰謀
And I think she's got something big planned.
你請他來了嗎
Did you get him?
當然
Of course.
哦 嗨
Oh! Hey.
你好啊
Hello!
哇哦
Wow.
等等 那是最高法院法官安東尼·肯尼迪嗎
What? Is that Supreme Court Justice Anthony Kennedy?
我肯定那是個冒牌貨
I'm sure it's just a lookalike.
嗯
Yeah.
那我們怎麼確定他不是呢
But how can we be sure?
聽說你們想
I was told the participants would like
盡快完成婚禮
to get this done quickly.
是的 我時日無多了
Yes. Um, I don't have much time left.
懂了
Understood.
請在這兒簽名
Sign here, please.
哦 謝謝
Oh. Okay. Thank you.
我需要一支筆 哦
Um, I need a pen... Oh.
謝謝你 海斯特
Thank you, Hester.
你太貼心了 親愛的
Sweet of you. Darling?
怎麼了
What?
哦
Hmm. Oh.
好的 就當已經公證過了
Okay. Assuming this gets notarized,
我宣佈你們是正式的夫妻了
I pronounce you husband and wife.
啊
Ah!
嗨
Hi.
抱歉 我知道你們不想被打擾
Sorry. I know you didn't want to be disturbed.
沒關係 夏奈爾五號
It's okay, Chanel #5.
我覺得這可能是你離婚姻最近的一次了
Considering that this is the closest you will ever get
所以這次就破例吧
to being married, I'm gonna make an exception.
謝謝 我研究了一下
Thank you. So, I have done some research,
看了你的測試結果
and looked over your tests,
我認為你沒有患上苦魯病 即使是患上了
and I don't think you have Kuru. And if you do,
也可能只是在第二階段而已
you're probably only in the second clinical stage...
就是久坐階段 這個階段的癥狀
the sedentary stage... and symptoms of that stage
包括沒有幫助的話無法自行走路
include not being able to walk without support.
-這癥狀我有啊 -她有啊
-Which I have. -She has that.
-顫抖呢 -看到沒
- Tremors. - See?
還有情緒不穩定 抑鬱
Emotional instability, depression.
這些我當然有
Which I certainly have, because you...
因為你正在浪費我僅剩的寶貴時間
are wasting what little precious time I have left.
我也查過庫魯病 好嗎
I, too, have researched Kuru, okay?
-苦魯病 -苦魯病
- Kuru. - Kuru.
當然 她的癥狀可能是因為其他的事情
And sure, her symptoms may be from something else,
但這位女士吃了死人肉 而那個人來自
but this woman ate dead flesh from the only known tribe
全世界唯一攜帶這種病的部落
to carry that disease on this planet.
抱歉 但我認為我們的診斷是正確的
I mean, I'm sorry, but I feel that our diagnosis is correct.
-抱歉 親愛的 -等等 要想確診的話
-I'm sorry, boo. -Wait, but the only way
唯一的方法就是做腦切片檢測
to really know for sure is to test a piece of her brain.
我們做個喚醒開顱手術來提取樣本 如何
What if we performed an awake craniotomy to get the sample?
如果她在手術中是清醒的
If she's awake during the operation,
我們可以問她問題
we can ask her questions to
來確保不錯切下
make sure that we're not getting close to any parts
她真正需要用的部分
that she actually needs.
你知道
You know,
大腦是一塊兒很神奇的肉
the brain is a weird piece of meat,
適應力很強 我是說
and it's highly adaptable, I mean...
但接下來幾周我就會變成植物人了
But I'll be a vegetable for the remaining weeks I have left.
你不是真的要考慮這件事吧 親愛的
You're not seriously considering this, are you, my love?
這麼說吧 如果你沒有苦魯病 而是其他可以治療的病
Just saying, it would really suck if you don't have Kuru
但因為我們不知道是哪種病
and you do have something that we could treat,
而你最後死了 那就慘了
but you die because we never knew.
而且這手術太牛逼了
Plus, it's a badass surgery,
我可以在我哈佛同學面前趾高氣昂了
I mean, I would look so cool in front of my friends at Harvard.
沒錯 我的母校是哈佛
That's the school I went to, Harvard.
你知道嗎
Y-You know...
你說的對
you're right.
如果我沒有苦魯病
If I don't have Kuru,
那就意味著我們倆可以一直在一起
that means you and I have years and years
一年一年又一年
and years and years of being together ahead of us.
那真是棒棒噠
That sounds great.
喂
Hello.
喂 霍菲護士嗎
Hello, Nurse Hoffel?
我是簡·霍利斯 卡西迪的媽媽
It's Jane Hollis, Cassidy's mom.
呃 我有點忙 能一會兒給你打回去嗎
Uh, I'm a little busy. Can I call you back?
哦 我很快就說完
Oh, I just need a minute.
你在哪兒 聽起來回聲好大
Where are you? It sounds like a big echo.
地下室
In the basement.
哦 聽起來很有意思
Ooh, that sounds fun.
是個設計完善的地下室嗎
Is it a finished basement?
我一直想要一個那樣的
I always wanted one of those...
簡 我真的很忙
Jane! I'm really sort of busy.
好吧 我切入主題
Right, I'll just get to it.
聽著
Listen.
我兒子現在對我來說就是個死人
My son is dead to me.
所以現在只有你和我了
So now it's just you and me.
我很感謝你一直以來做的事情
I really appreciate all the work you've been doing,
我想幫你結束這個工作
and I wanted to offer my help in finishing the job.
我覺得我自己挺好的 謝謝了
I think I'm doing fine on my own. Thank you.
哦
Oh.
她掛了
She hung up.
我含辛茹苦 將他養大
I did everything right, raising that boy.
到頭來 我是個失敗的母親
All I know is, I'm a failure as a mother.
呃 聽著
Mm. Look,
也許你這麼想的原因
maybe you're feeling that way
是你覺得卡西迪做的事情讓你失望了
because you're seeing what Cassidy did as letting you down.
他做得很對
He did the right thing.
這意味著他內心深處是個好人
Which means deep down, he's a good person
是非分明
who knows right from wrong.
誰教的他這些呢
Who taught him that?
呃 他經常看電視
Well, he watches a lot of television.
《摩登家庭》對他影響很深
Modern Family impacted him deeply.
是你
It was you.
我知道失去愛人的感覺
I know what it's like to lose someone you love.
我男朋友被人謀殺了
My boyfriend was murdered.
我每天都想念他強壯的臂彎
I miss his big arm muscles every day.
我也好想我丈夫
I miss my husband so much.
他的臂彎沒有那麼強壯
His arm muscles weren't very big,
但它們曾是屬於我的
but they were mine.
如果你總是集中於復仇
As long as you keep focusing on revenge,
你就無法真正地哀悼他
you'll never get to truly grieve him.
讓我帶你看看這家醫院吧
Let me show you the hospital.
你兒子幫助建立了這家新醫院
The new one your son helped build?
真正治癒他人的新醫院
The one that actually heals people.
你不能參加
You can't go through with this.
-為什麼 -如果你治好了她怎麼辦
- Why? - Because what if you cure her?
我不可能治好她的
I'm not gonna cure her.
我會繼續做這個手術
Look, I'm gonna go ahead with the procedure,
然後我會發現她還是會死
I'm gonna find out she's still dying,
我們哭一哭 來一發安慰啪
we'll cry a bunch, we'll probably pound some,
幾周以後 她就死了
and then, in a few weeks, she's gonna die
你和我就去血島
and you and I will go to Blood Island.
-我想殺了她 -啥
- I want you to kill her. - What?
噓
Shh!
不 我想讓你在手術中殺了她
No. I want you to kill her during her surgery,
弄得像是一起事故一樣
and make it look like an accident. Just say that you...
就像是你突然想起《隔山有眼2》中的場景
remembered a scene, from Hills Have Eyes 2,
你想要克服那些恐懼
and you were overcome with chills, like...
啊 我突然想起了《隔山有眼2》中的場景
I just remembered a scene from Hills Have Eyes 2
我就這麼劃開了她的腦子 我就是個蠢蛋
and I just sliced open her brain. I'm such a klutz,
我再也不要在手術之前
and I'm never gonna watch a scary movie ever again
-看恐怖片了 -我等不了了
-before a surgery. -I can't wait any longer.
知道嗎 她必須死 我想喝著雞尾酒
Okay? She's got to go. I want to be sipping on Mai Tais,
一周內一直追殺那些遊客
and I want to be hunting down tourists within a week.
姑娘 冷靜 控制你自己
Woman, calm down. Get ahold of yourself.
我不會在手術期間殺了她的
I will not kill her during this surgery.
如果我把這場手術弄砸了 我的名聲就毀了
If I botch this up, my reputation will be destroyed.
整個計劃是以蒙施教務長的死為前提的
Okay, this whole plan depends on Dean Munsch being dead.
如果她活了下來
And if she's alive,
那她就能保住她的財產 我就得回去坐牢了
then she gets to keep her money, and I have to go back to prison,
在監獄裏我就得靠自己畫的春宮圖自慰
where I literally have to draw porn to masturbate to,
而我畫畫超級爛的
and I am a terrible artist.
我不想再過那種日子了
I'm not gonna do that again.
不要
No.
所以你給我在手術期間殺了她
So you kill her during the surgery,
不然的話
or else.
不然怎樣
Or else what?
你聽到我說的話了
Oh. You heard me.
不然
Or else.
我知道 我知道 不然怎樣
I know... I know, or else what?
不然
Or else.
聽著 夏奈爾們
Listen. Chanels.
我要跟你們說個小秘密
I'm going to let you in on a little secret.
我之前只是假裝不在意布洛克娶蒙施教務長
I was only pretending to be cool with Brock marrying Dean Munsch.
事實是 我對此非常不爽
Really, I'm not cool with it.
你其實之前看起來就是很不爽
You actually didn't seem cool with it at all.
SSK字幕組
非常明顯
It was very obvious.
SSK字幕組
我跟你們講
I'm gonna tell you something.
我討厭蒙施教務長
I hate Dean Munsch.
我討厭她讓我們把那些噁心的
I hated her when she made us take those gross pledges
後來全被殺了的預備會員帶去卡帕聯誼會
into Kappa House that all got murdered,
這基本上讓我們逃脫了被謀殺的命運
which basically prevented us from getting murdered.
我討厭她把我們
I hated her when she plucked
從一貧如洗中解脫出來
us out of abject poverty and let us come
讓我們來到她的醫學院學習 毫無疑問
to her medical school, no questions asked,
這讓我們實現了畢生夢想
when then led us to fulfilling
成為上電視的醫生
our lifelong dream of becoming TV doctors...
我的意思是 例子還有很多
I mean, the list goes on.
我被嫉妒壓垮了
I'm crushed with jealousy.
我的意思是 嫉妒把我推倒
I mean, jealousy has pinned
坐在我胸口放屁
me down and is sitting on my chest and farting.
那你打算怎麼樣呢
So what are you gonna do?
這是一杯滾燙的南瓜拿鐵
This is a pipin' hot pumpkin spice latte.
一旦蒙施的頭在手術中被打開 大腦暴露之時
Once Munsch's head is sawed open and her brain is exposed,
我就把這杯南瓜拿鐵
I'm gonna throw this pumpkin spice latte
倒在她裸露的大腦上
into her open brain.
什麼
What, what?
我要把這杯南瓜拿鐵倒在她裸露的大腦上
I'm gonna throw this latte into her open brain.
我聽到了 但是為什麼呢
I heard you, but why?
這會殺了她
It'll kill her!
會嗎
Will it?
當然會了
Of course it will.
這
Um, I'm not...
這可不好說
I'm not sure that it will.
或許能灼傷腦組織
I mean, it might scald a layer of brain tissue,
但應該不會留下什麼永久性傷害
but I don't think it'll leave any lasting damage.
更何況她根本感覺不到
Plus, she won't even feel it.
所以 或許會稍微灼傷
So it'll maybe scald,
她大腦的一小部分
like, a tiny little section of her brain
但會立刻痊癒
and then it'll heal right away.
你在逗我嗎 夏奈爾五號
Are you kidding me, Number Five?
往別人大腦裏倒入
It's not "Doing someone a favor"
無比滾燙而美味的
to pour really scalding, super-delicious
南瓜拿鐵又不是什麼好事
pumpkin spice latte into their open brain.
就是啊 如果真的很燙的話
It is, if it's actually scalding.
事實是 如果真的很燙
Just the fact that it's scalding means
會立刻燙死
that any bacteria
所有細菌
would be killed instantly.
你要做的是
What you should do is get one
拿一杯常溫拿鐵
at room temperature and leave it out
放置幾天 等到它壞了
for a couple of days until it spoils,
然後再倒進她的大腦
and then pour it on her open brain.
可是馬上就要動手術了
Okay, well, the surgery is happening
夏奈爾五號 我們沒那麼多時間
right now, Number Five, so we don't have three days.
你什麼時候變得這麼聰明了
And since when did you become so smart?
我可是靠自己高分通過了醫考
Since I aced the MCATs with no help.
又來了
Ugh, this again.
我們都高分通過了 夏奈爾五號
We all aced the MCATs, Number Five.
我就是不明白你為什麼非要殺了她
I just don't know why you have to kill her.
反正她馬上就要死了
I mean, she's gonna die soon anyway.
我不想讓她就這樣死了
I don't want her to die.
我想讓她被我殺死
I want her to be killed by me.
所以我要假裝不小心被絆倒
That's why I am gonna pretend to trip,
然後把這杯滾燙的南瓜拿鐵倒進她的大腦
and pour this piping-hot PSL into her open brain.
別廢話了 就這樣 我一定要這麼做
End of conversation. Deal with it. It's happening!
我不確定 我不在乎
I'm not gonna... I don't even care.
她並沒有在聽
She's not listening.
蒙施教務長
Dean Munsch.
嗯
Hm?
我鋸開了你一小塊顱骨
I've sawed open a small section of your skull.
霍爾特醫生馬上就開始動手術了
Dr. Holt's starting the procedure right now.
你能聽到嗎
Can you hear me?
我怎麼了
Wha-What am I on?
我們在你脖子上做了神經阻斷術
We performed a nerve block
這樣你就不會感覺到疼痛了
in your neck so you won't feel any pain,
我會給你注射一些氯硝西泮
and I've given you a mild dose of clonazepam
讓你放鬆些
- to keep you calm. - Mmm.
放鬆
Calm?
好吧 我感覺很好
Okay. I feel great.
你給我開顱 將我的大腦組織
I mean, you opened up my brain
暴露在外
and exposed it to the world.
但你知道嗎
But you know,
-好戲即將開始 -好了
- party on, whatever. - All right, now...
接下來
What I'm gonna do is insert this biopsy needle
我要將活檢針穿過額葉中
in through a section of the frontal lobe
控制歌唱功能的區域
that processes music.
所以如果可以的話 我希望你能唱首歌
So I'd like you to sing a song for us, if you can.
你有喜歡的歌嗎
Is there a song that you like?
有 《水上煙霧》
Yeah, "Smoke on the Water."
深紫樂隊的《水上煙霧》
Deep Purple, "Smoke on the Water."
-真的嗎 -是啊
- Seriously? - Well, yeah.
他們可是重金屬搖滾樂的元老級組合啊
I mean, they're like the granddaddies of heavy metal.
你沒聽過他們的和弦嗎
Have you never heard that chord progression?
我說真的
I mean, seriously.
#我們一行人來到蒙特勒鎮#
# We all came down to Montreux #
#在日內瓦湖的濱線上#
# On the Lake Geneva shoreline #
#用移動錄音車錄製專輯#
# To make records with a mobile #
#我們的時間不多#
# We didn't have much time #
插入活檢針
Inserting biopsy needle.
#水上煙霧#
# Smoke on the water #
#火光沖天#
# A fire in the sky #
穿過胼胝體
Passing through the corpus callosum.
#煙#
# Smooooo... #
我肯定碰到什麼了
Oop, must've hit something.
#霧#
# ...oooooooke #
#之於上水#
# On the water #
#嗒嗒嗒#
# Dun dun dunh #
#嗒嗒嗒嗒#
# Dun dun duh-nuh #
#嗒嗒嗒嗒嗒#
# Dun dun dunh, dun dunh #
-取出病變組織 -#嘿 嗒嗒嗒#
- Taking the biopsy now. - # Hey, dun dun dunh #
#嗒嗒嗒嗒#
# Dun dun duh-nuh #
霍菲護士 紗布
Nurse Hoffel, gauze.
#嗒嗒嗒嗒嗒#
# Dun dun dunh, dun dunh #
#水上煙霧#
# Smoke on the water #
#火光沖天#
# A fire in the sky... #
你在幹什麼
What the hell are you doing?!
抱歉 我被絆了一下
I'm sorry, I tripped.
-才沒有 -我沒幹壞事
- No, you didn't. - I-I didn't do anything.
-滾出去 -我只是不小心
- No, get out! - I'm just a patsy.
我們縫合創口吧
Okay, let's sew her back up.
五號 請把樣本送到檢驗室
Five, let's get this sample down to the lab, please.
卡西迪 縫合吧
Cassidy, close up the hole.
親愛的
Okay, well, honey,
手術進行得非常順利
the procedure went perfectly,
除了夏奈爾弄灑了一杯拿鐵之外
except for Chanel throwing a latte.
我們會進行縫合 你會恢復得很好的
We're gonna stitch you up, and you're gonna be
很快就能
as good as new.
上床了嗎
Mmm. Boning soon?
沒錯 寶貝
That's right, sweetheart.
-床上見 -太好了
- Boning soon. - Excellent.
蒙施教務長 我有一個好消息
Dean Munsch, I have some good news.
也有一個壞消息
I also have some bad news.
我們沒發現苦魯病的跡象
We found no evidence of Kuru.
什麼
- Oh! - What?
-太好了 -但是好消息是
- Wonderful! - But the good news is...
-等等 那不是好消息嗎 -那是壞消息
- Wait, that's not the good news? - That's the bad news.
也就意味著檢測還沒有得出定論
That means that the test was inconclusive.
也就是說你仍然很有可能
And that means that it's still very likely
患有苦魯病
that you could have Kuru.
那好消息是什麼
So what's the good news?
好消息是
The good news is that
你仍然可能會死
you'll probably still die.
而且你已經準備好去死了
And you've been preparing for that.
所以你不需要再準備什麼了
So no further preparations are needed,
你可以繼續做愛做的事
and, um, you can just, uh, keep doing what you're doing.
你對病人態度真差
You have terrible bedside manner.
我還有其他的有趣消息
Well, there's also interesting news.
我查了一下其他可能和苦魯病
I looked up other things that could cause the symptoms
有相同癥狀的疾病
we all think is Kuru
唯一能造成
and the only thing that could be causing
相同癥狀的情況是
all of those symptoms...
脫水
dehydration.
-什麼 -嚴重脫水
- What? - Extreme dehydration.
比如你得達到幾年不喝水的程度
Like, you would have had to not have water for years.
胡說 我喝水的啊
That's insane. I drink water.
我經常喝東西
I mean, I'm constantly drinking.
我
I-I...
天啊
Oh, my God.
我只喝威士忌
I only drink scotch.
或者伏特加
Or vodka.
等等 這不可能啊
Wait, wait, wait, wait. That doesn't make any sense.
你會在酒裏兌水吧
You put water in it, don't you?
或者放冰塊進去
Or drink it on the rocks?
不加 我喝純的
No. Straight up. Neat.
好吧 但你總會攝入少量的水吧
Okay, but you'd have to have a little bit of water.
你刷牙的時候
I mean, you brush your teeth,
漱口用的
and you rinse with...
威士忌
Scotch.
好吧 那你去餐廳吃飯的時候呢
Okay, um, what about at a restaurant?
您喝蒸餾水還是蘇打水
Would you like still or sparkling?
我想要兩指深的威士忌 純的
Actually, I'd love two fingers of scotch, neat.
謝謝
Thank you.
等等 你認為我只是嚴重缺水嗎
I'm sorry, so you think I am just extremely dehydrated?
可我吃過人腦的事怎麼解釋呢
But what about the fact that I ate brains?
喂 斯萬多 我是凱西·蒙施
Hello, Swando? It's Cathy Munsch.
你還記得我嗎 我們在飛機上遇到的
Do you remember me? We met on a plane.
凱西 好長時間沒見了
Cathy, hi. It's been a while.
是我 斯萬多
Yes, hello, Swando.
你還記得你帶我去的那場派對嗎
Um, do you remember that party that you took me to?
那是你的一個親戚的葬禮 對嗎
That was for one of your relatives, am I correct?
對的 很傷感
Yes, that is right. Very sad.
我們還吃了腦子
And we ate brains?
對的對的
Yes, that is right.
那是家族傳統
It's a family tradition.
我得了苦魯病
I have Kuru.
-噢凱西 我為你感到難過 -好了 好了 好了
- Oh, Cathy, that's very sad. - There, there. There, there.
我們也很心碎
We are heartbroken, too.
祖父是家族裏至親的一員
Grandpa was a dear member of the family.
蘭比也是
And so was Lamby.
等等 等等 誰是蘭比
Wait, wait, who's Lamby?
蘭比是我們的寵物羊 它也死了
Lamby. He was our pet lamb. He died, too.
根據家族的習慣 每當寵物羊死的時候
It's a family tradition that when a pet lamb dies,
我們就會把它的腦子吃掉
we eat the brains.
等等 你是說我吃的是羊腦
Wait, are you saying that I ate lamb brains
而不是人腦
and not human brains?
我們當然不吃人腦啦
Of course we don't eat human brains,
你這排外的垃圾
you xenophobic piece of garbage.
我沒得苦魯病
I don't have Kuru!
我只是脫水
I'm dehydrated.
我馬上就會痊癒了
I'm gonna be fine.
噢 噢
Oh! Oh...
嘿 霍菲護士想讓大家都
Hey, everybody, Nurse Hoffel wants us all
去地下室
to go down to the basement
共飲香檳
for a champagne toast
來慶祝一個好消息
to celebrate the good news.
她怎麼會知道 噢 來吧
How does she know? Oh, come on.
我得喝點水
I need some water.
歡迎大家
Welcome, everyone.
請進
Please go inside.
噢 香檳和芝士
Oh, champagne and cheese!
還有蜜月床
And a honeymoon bed.
親愛的 床上見啦
Sweetheart, boning soon!
等等
Hold on a second.
這不是香檳 這是蘋果酒
This isn't real champagne. This is sparkling apple cider!
芝士也是泡沫塑料做的
And this cheese is Styrofoam.
我只想讓你們最後的晚餐
I just wanted to make sure your last meal was
越噁心越好
as awful as possible.
等等
Wait.
你是綠衣惡鬼
You're the Green Meanie?
我倒是沒有想到
Well, I was not expecting that.
海斯特 你本可以
Well, Hester, you could have given...
-海斯特在哪兒 -我幾個小時前
- Where's Hester? - I saw her get in an Uber
看到她拎著行李進了一輛出租車
with her suitcases a couple of hours ago.
她肯定是逃走了
Pretty sure she was running away.
-不知道為什麼花了那麼久 -這不合情理啊
- Not sure why it took her so long. - This makes no sense.
她年紀太大了 肯定不是那個遺腹子
She's way to old to be the baby in the belly.
那你們也別說我啊
That didn't stop you guys accusing me.
卡西迪才是那個嬰兒
Dr. Cassidy is the baby in the belly,
也是另一個綠衣惡鬼
and the other Green Meanie.
他已經大概三天沒有殺人了
He totally hasn't killed someone in, like, three days, so...
這和禍肥護士
What does any of this have to do
有什麼關係
with Nurse Awful?!
因為我的真名不是「霍菲」
Because my real name isn't "Hoffel,"
你這邪惡的小蕩婦
you evil little trollop.
我姓比恩
It's Bean!
聽起來很耳熟嗎
Sort of rings a bell?
噢天哪 阿加莎·比恩
Oh, for the love of Pete! Agatha Bean?
你能再給點提示嗎
Can you give us a couple more clues?
她是你們的女傭
She was your maid!
你把可憐的阿加莎按到了油鍋裏
You burned poor Agatha's face in the deep fryer.
噢
Oh...
她是我的姐姐 而你殺了她
She was my sister, and you killed her.
而你就這麼放過了她們 蒙施教務長
And you let them get away with it, Dean Munsch.
-我很抱歉 -我可以說句話嗎
- I am sooo sorry about that. - Can I just say...
我覺得我被無辜地
I feel like I'm unfairly being, you know,
放到了這組人中間
lumped in with this group here.
附帶損害
Collateral damage.
今天她們會為她們對可憐的阿加莎做的事
Today they pay for what they did
付出代價
to sweet Agatha.
而卡西迪將會做替罪羊
And Cassidy will take the fall for all of it.
等等
Not so fast!
媽媽
Mom?
澤達 你還活著
Zayday, you're safe!
噢 那我放心了
Oh, I'm so relieved.
謝謝你們為了找我
Yeah, thank you guys for all your tireless efforts
做的無用功
in trying to find me.
我又一次被困在了井裏
I was trapped in a well again.
這事就這麼結束了吧 霍菲護士
This ends now, Nurse Hoffel.
自從看到了這所醫院
Since seeing this hospital,
它關愛 尊重 治癒病人的方式
and the way it loves, respects, and heals its patients,
讓我明白我該放下憤怒的執念了
it's made me realize how wrong I was to hold onto my anger.
過去的事就過去了
The past is the past.
我重生了
I'm reborn!
把她放到籠子裏
Put her in the cage!
-讓讓 讓讓 -快讓讓
- Move it! Move it! - Come on, move it.
不 不
No, no! Aww.
媽媽
Mom.
對不起我讓你失望了
I'm so sorry I let you down.
不不 你沒有
No. No, you didn't.
你救了我
You saved me.
你和澤達·威廉姆斯
You and Zayday Williams.
霍利斯女士
Ms. Hollis, I'm so sorry
對於你和你家人的遭遇 我很是難過
about everything that's happened to you and your family.
如果我們逃過了這劫
And if we make it through this,
我發誓這所醫院會盡力治癒更多人
I promise this hospital will make amends
來作為補償
by caring for and curing as many people as possible.
你爸爸
Your father.
一定會為你驕傲的
He would be so proud.
我要殺了你
I'm gonna kill you.
那可有點難呢
Well, that's gonna be a little difficult
你馬上就要被
when you're splattered into a million pieces
炸成粉身碎骨了
all over the neighborhood.
這個炸彈比雲圖還大
This is a bigger bomb than Cloud Atlas!
祝賀你 卡西迪
Congratulations, Cassidy.
我覺得你媽媽終於得償所願了
I think your mommy's about to get her wish.
我唯一的遺憾
The only regret I have
就是不能看著你
is that I don't get to see your face
臨死前的樣子 夏奈爾
when you finally die, Chanel.
再見了 夏奈爾們 祝你們在地獄玩得愉快
Good-bye, Chanels. Have fun in hell.
噢 對了 我聽說
Oh, by the way, I heard
地獄裏沒有恐龍
there are no dinosaurs!
噢 不
Oh, no.
好吧
Oh. Okay.
我覺得我們或許應該
I guess we should
用現在的時間
take this moment,
來放下一些怨恨
perhaps, to let go of some old grudges.
放屁 我要出去
Screw that, I am going out
大幹一番
guns blazing!
等等 等等
Wait! Wait a minute!
-什麼 丹妮絲 -什麼
- Wha... Denise! - What?
你還活著 說明我的低溫室奏效了
You're alive, that means my cryo-chamber worked!
當然啦 蒙施
Damn right it did, crunchy Munsch.
低溫讓我的心跳跳得足夠慢
The low temperature allowed my heart to beat slowly enough
來重新獲得能量還不是怎麼的
to regain its strength or something.
不管怎麼樣
Anyway,
我回來啦 賤人們 好了
I'm back, bitches! All right.
我錯過了什麼
What did I miss?
噢 希拉裏怎麼樣了
Ooh! How's Hillary working out?
我是指我們的第一位女性總統
I mean, the first female president,
我居然錯過了那一刻
and I missed the moment!
-該死的 -你就不能別講了
- Damn it! - Can you just stop talking
先把炸彈拆了
and defuse the bomb?
該死 那個看起來好複雜
Damn, that look complicated.
匡蒂科可沒教我怎麼拆炸彈
They didn't show us how to defuse no bombs in Quantico.
但是 但是 但是
But, but, but, but, but
萬幸的是
fortunate for all of us,
我看過《諜網》裏
I did watch the hit TV show Quantico.
亞歷克斯·帕裏什探員是怎麼拆炸彈的
And I saw Agent Alex Parrish defuse one.
好吧
All right.
如果我記得沒錯的話
If my memory serves me correctly...
該死的 我沒帶眼鏡 但是我覺得
Damn, I don't have my glasses. Okay, but I think
如果我拉下那根線 要麼
if I pull that wire, either...
倒數會停止
the countdown will stop,
要麼 我們都會被炸成碎片
or we'll all be blown to smithereens.
只有一個辦法來證明了
Ain't but one damn way to find out.
我確實有陰齒
I do have teeth in my vagina!
我就知道
I knew it.
我不想作為一個騙子死去
I didn't want to die a liar.
它們很鋒利
They are very sharp.
我不知道它們怎麼會長進去的
And I don't know how they got there.
閉嘴吧
Shut up!
噢
Oh!
太好了
Yes!
噢 丹妮絲
Oh, Denise!
丹妮絲·亨普希爾
Denise Hemphill.
哈哈
Ha!
抓住她
Let's get her!
噢 天哪
Oh, God.
你為我犧牲了自己
You sacrificed yourself for me.
你知道的 兄弟 你本可以把她推開
You know, pal, could've just pushed her out of the way
來救她
to save her life.
是啊
Yeah.
以身擋刀可不是最好的方法
Jumping in front of a machete is, like, option number three
來救夏奈爾三號
in terms of the ways you could've kept Chanel #3 alive.
閉嘴
Shut up.
這是他的救贖
This was his redemption.
現在他抵過了
Now he can be forgiven
殺人的罪
for killing all those people.
我可不覺得事情是這麼運作的
Uh, I don't think it works that way.
閉嘴
Shut up!
他想要說話
He's trying to speak.
現在你要死了
Now that you're dying,
還相信自己一直活著嗎
do you believe that you were always alive?
我知道我還活著
I knew I was alive...
因為愛你真好
because of how good it felt to love you.
啊 現在說什麼呢
Uh, say what now?
她要逃跑了 快走
She's getting away. Go!
她在那兒呢
There she is!
她要逃跑了
She getting away!
噢 當心 流沙
Oh! Careful, quicksand.
誰給我根繩子
Somebody! Drop me a rope!
快點 這樣死去太慘了
Come on! This is a horrible way to die.
聽著 以我的經驗來說
Look, in my experience,
連環殺手
costumed serial killers
從來不會在法律上得到相應的制裁
are never adequately punished by the law.
有時候私法是唯一的解決方式
Sometimes vigilante justice is the only way.
我支持夏奈爾 她殺了我的男朋友
I'm with Chanel. She killed my boyfriend.
噢 我猜沒人關心你男朋友
Oh, so I suppose no one cares
殺了我男朋友吧
that your boyfriend murdered my boyfriend?!
不 沒人關心
No! No one does.
好吧 我們來投票
All right. We'll take a vote.
支持救霍菲護士的舉手
All in favor of saving Nurse Hoffel, raise your hand.
支持淹死她的舉手
All in favor of a terrible swamp death, raise your hand.
哈
Boom.
我 噢
I... Oh...
噢 我該死的道德心
Oh! Damn my conscience!
給你
Here.
-拿著 -什麼
- Here. - What...
好了 抓住
Okay, hold on!
幫我一把 抓住
Help me. Hold...
等等 等等 好了
Wait, wait. Okay.
-抓住 -噢
- Hold on. Oh... - Oh!
就像那樣 另一群瘋狂的連環殺手
And just like that, another group of crazy serial killers
沒能毀掉我
failed in their mission to destroy me.
不 不 不 不
No! No! No! No!
我知道 通常能在這些事情當中堅持到最後的女孩
I know the last girl standing in these things is usually
都是甜美純真的女英雄 但根據我的經驗
some sweet, virginal heroine. But in my experience,
想要倖存就得苗條 漂亮 時尚
survival is all about being skinny, pretty, fashionable
無情 我不知道那些因素為什麼那麼重要
and ruthless. I don't know why those things matter,
但我就是那樣的人 並且我還活著
but that's who I am and I'm still alive.
所以 根據這個事實 那一定就是原因
So, ipso facto, that must be why.
不必再懼怕一個連環殺手
Not being terrorized by a serial killer
給醫院帶來了奇跡
did wonders for the hospital.
也讓夏奈爾五號得到快樂
Which made Chanel #5 supes happy.
我知道 截至目前 所有你去看過的醫生
Now, I know all the doctors you've seen up to this point
都認為你有代謝綜合征 但通過觀察你的家族病史
think you have MS, but looking at your family history,
我認為你很有可能有潛在的血管疾病
I think it's possible you could have a hidden vascular issue,
所有我打算給你做一個核磁共振成像
so I'm gonna order an MRI.
看來一遇到醫學問題
Turns out she's some kind of idiot savant
她就成了天才白癡
when it comes to medical stuf.
她還是那麼不可容忍並且孤身一人 顯而易見
She's still intolerable and single, obvi,
但至少她為這個世界做了些好事
but at least she's doing some good in the world.
現在布洛克和蒙施教務長
And now that Brock and Dean Munsch
離開了醫院 她和澤達
left the hospital, she and Zayday
就成了這裏的掌權人
are kind of top dogs there.
如果我們和聖瑪麗醫院
If we form an alliance with St. Mary's Hospital
還有KHF醫院組成聯盟 我們可以合作保持低價
and KHF Hospital, we can coordinate to keep prices low.
這會削減我們的利潤 但是我們在這兒
It might cut into our profits, but we're here
是為了給人們治病 而不是為了賺錢 對吧
to cure people, not make money, right?
行啊 沒問題
Well, okay.
哦 但是蒙施教務長和霍特醫生沒有一起離開
Oh, Dean Munsch and Dr. Hot didn't leave together, though.
霍菲護士成為沼澤最後一名受害者那天
Major drama went down the day Nurse Hoffel
主要戲劇就進入了尾聲
became the swamp's final victim.
我們得談談
We need to talk.
嗯 哦 我英俊的丈夫
Mm. Oh, my beautiful husband.
自從他們在《摔角手》裏塑造了米基·洛克
I feel like I have been given the greatest second chance
我覺得我就像被賜予了第二次最偉大的機會
since they cast Mickey Rourke in The Wrestler.
現在你要看著我變老 我要看著
Now you get to watch me grow old and I get to see
你是不是真的會變老 或者你就像人們說的那樣
if you'll actually grow old or if you're a vampire
是個長生不老的吸血鬼
who never ages, like everyone says.
大家真的都那麼說嗎
Does everybody really say that?
是的 但是
Yeah. But...
沒關係 因為重要的是
it doesn't matter, because what matters
這家醫院會變成它對外宣傳的那樣
is that this hospital gets to be what it claims to be:
一個治療疑難雜癥的地方
a place where the incurable are cured.
我可以放心地
I'll have no problem
把它交到另一個的手裏
finding somebody to take it off my hands.
沒錯 這是個好主意 你可以去環遊世界或幹點別的什麼
Well, yeah, that's a good idea. You should travel the world
我會留在這裏
or whatever, and I will stay here
我會為你守住城堡
and I will hold down the fort for you,
我會思念你 親愛的
and I will miss you, my darling.
別傻了 我的愛人
Don't be silly, hubby o' mine.
你看 我現在就要去銀行
You see, I am going to the bank right now
把我所有的錢都取出來
and I'm pulling out all my money.
然後你和我可以去阿斯彭
Then you and I are going to buy
買一座小木屋
a chalet in Aspen,
我會掛牌開業
and I am gonna hang out a shingle
成為對於五十歲以上的女人來說最好的性治療專家
and become the premier sex therapist for women over 50
而你 我的愛人
and you, my love,
會成為明星們的
are gonna be the orthopedic surgeon
整容醫生
to the stars.
愛你
Love you.
對不起 有什麼問題嗎
I'm sorry, is there a problem?
這真的很尷尬 但是
This is rather awkward, but...
您的賬戶已經沒有錢了 蒙施教務長
your accounts are empty, Dean Munsch.
什麼
Excuse me?
你幾天前來過
You came in earlier today
-並取走了你所有的存款 -什麼
- and withdrew all of your funds. - What?!
照片照得不大好
It's not a great picture.
沒錯 海斯特偷走了蒙施教務長所有的錢
Yup, Hester stole all of Dean Munsch's money.
還有她的男人 不過沒有人知道他們逃到哪裏去了
And her man. Though no one knows where they ran off to.
先生 您要現在用午餐還是稍後再用
Will you be having lunch now, sir, or later?
我不知道 你覺得呢 甜心
I don't know. What do you think, sweetie?
客人們到了嗎
Have the guests arrived?
大概半個小時之前 他們的船觸礁了
Their boat hit the reef about half an hour ago.
那些強壯的人隨時會游上岸
The strongest ones should be swimming ashore at any moment.
我們現在就吃飯吧 給他們一個機會補充能量
Let's eat now and give 'em a chance to get their energy back.
-謝謝你 先生 -在他們都筋疲力竭的時候
- Thank you, sir. - It's no fun
去捕捉他們是毫無樂趣的
hunting them when they're all worn out.
嗯 我贊同
Ugh. I agree.
看來我們想的一樣
It's like we have the same brain.
血島
愛之專家
不過蒙施教務長沒用多久就重新站起來了
Dean Munsch didn't take long to get back on her feet, though.
她賣了醫院 得到一大筆錢去了阿斯彭
She sold the hospital for a fortune and went to Aspen
幫助老女人們記住如何再次獲得性高潮
to help old ladies remember how to have orgasms again.
愛之專家
梅雷迪思 進來
Meredith. Come on in.
她還啪了半支美國滑雪隊
She's also boning half the U.S. Ski Team.
至於我 就像命中注定
And as for me, well, destiny called...
好吧 是命運傳呼了我 因為現在是2016年了
well, destiny DM'd me, because it's 2016
沒有人會真的再打電話了
and no one actually calls anymore.
SSK字幕組
這裏是《麻辣醫生愛上我》
It's Lovin' the C,
SSK字幕組
有請主持人 夏奈爾·奧伯林醫生
with your host, Dr. Chanel Oberlin!
沒錯 我現在是一個電視醫生 就像我曾經說的那樣
Yup, I'm a TV doctor, just like I said I would be.
因為我獲得了我應得的
Because I get what I deserve,
我值得擁有我得到的一切
and I deserve everything I get.
夏奈爾三號是我的蓋爾王
Chanel #3 is my Gayle King.
她是這個節目的執行製片人 管它是什麼呢
She executive produces the show, whatever that means.
嗨 大家好 歡迎來到《麻辣醫生愛上我》
Hi, everybody, and welcome to Lovin' the C.
我是夏奈爾·奧伯林醫生
I'm the C, Dr. Chanel Oberlin,
今天的節目 我們將討論死亡勸進小組
and today on the show we'll be discussing death panels.
對於想更快地得到遺產的有錢人來說
How can we make them a real thing
我們要怎麼把勸進小組變成真的呢
for rich people who want their inheritances sooner?
我想講兩句題外話
If I may be obliged
我很感激大家
a personal moment...
過去幾年間我學到了許多
I've learned a lot in the past few years,
其中最重要的是
and most importantly of all,
我學到了 你必須做你自己
I've learned that you just have to be yourself.
那些後果和責任
And that consequences and responsibility
對於感到羞愧的人來說是一個負擔
are burdens for people who choose to feel shame.
所以 做你們自己吧 美國人
So, you be you, America.
因為夏奈爾·奧伯林會繼續做自己
Because Chanel Oberlin is gonna keep being me.
富貴州
最美聯邦州